http://www.africanaquatic.com/index.php?main_page=privacy

Shop Menu
OSI Retail FoodsOSI Bulk FlakeOSI Bulk PelletsFry & Hatchery FoodsKoi & GoldfishFish House SuppliesSeachem ProductsCichlid PressSpecials ...New Products ...
Articles
Coming Soon...
At AFRICAN AQUATIC ,
your privacy is our priority. We are committed to protecting your privacy at
all times, in all situations. The information we collect about you when you
become a member is used to process your orders and to provide a more
personalized experience on our site. Our site uses a 128 bit encrypted SSL to
increase the security of our customer’s information. However, we “AFRICAN AQUATIC” do not
guarantee complete security on stored information, however, we have installed
and applied our encrypted pages and installed our SSL certificate to prevent
stolen information.
How Do We Use the Information We Collect?
When you become an “AFRICAN AQUATIC” member, we ask you to fill out a form that requests your name, address and
e-mail address as well as some demographic information such as gender and date
of birth.
“AFRICAN AQUATIC” will NOT share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis.
Your name and address information is used solely to process
orders unless your prior consent is given. Without your consent, this
information will NEVER be sold, given, rented or traded to others for purposes
other than order fulfillment.
Your demographic information (gender, date of birth, etc.)
will be used for several security purposes, to ensure you are who you say you
are and in fact you are paying with your credit cards and not someone using
your stolen credit cards.
Refer-A-Friend
If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we
will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically
send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. “AFRICAN AQUATIC” does not
store this information and uses it for the sole purpose of sending this
one-time email.
Our Use of Log Files
When you visit our site we automatically log your IP address, your browser type
and your access times. We utilize this information to conduct site performance
evaluations, to see where visitors are coming from and to keep track of click
stream data (the screens our users visit on our site). This data helps us to
determine what content our members find most appealing so that we can maximize
your enjoyment of the site. Log files are not tied to personally identifiable
information.
Site Security
All “AFRICAN AQUATIC” employees take your personal information very seriously. All employees must
learn and obey our security policies. Access to member personal information is
limited to key management personnel and our member services department. The
information is ID and password protected and our Web security is reviewed on a
monthly basis. We have also installed and implied our site with a 128 bit
encryption SSL.
Correcting/Updating Your Personal Information
After becoming an “AFRICAN AQUATIC” subscriber you may correct/update your personal information by clicking on the
'My Account' link at the top of any page, entering your ID, password and birth
date when prompted and clicking the Edit Information button. The changes you
make will be reflected in our databases instantly. If you wish to deactivate
your account, you may contact our member services group through the 'My
Account' section, or the 'Contact Us' section.
Links To Other Sites
This Web site contains links to other Web sites. Please note that when you
click on one of these links, you may be leaving the “AFRICAN AQUATIC” site and entering another Web site.
These sites may independently collect or request information about you and we
encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their
privacy policy may differ from ours.
Communication
From time to time we may send out email messages alerting you that products are
available, to remind you about providing feedback or for promotional offers. In
addition, you will receive communication from us 1) if you contact us for a
particular reason, 2) to receive your orders, or 3) we need to contact you for
administrative purposes such as winning a contest. Administrative e-mails will
not contain promotional materials. If you choose to receive our News Letters,
they will contain promotional materials from “AFRICAN AQUATIC”.
Legal Disclaimer
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose
personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief
that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a
court order or legal process served on our Web site
Supplementation
We may correct or supplement your address information with standardized postal
representation in order to ensure that your orders are delivered. We do this
since we want to make sure that our members receive the order and to lower
costs associated with our programs.
Contests
Periodically, contests are run on our site. Sometimes contests are sponsored by
our customers. To enter these contests you need only to enter your ID and
password and your guess. At the time of entry, you may decide if you wish to
have your first name and state posted on our site if you are the winner.
Winner’s names are NEVER shared with our customers without their consent.
Our Use of Cookies
Cookies are pieces of information that your browser stores on your computer's
hard drive which identify you when you enter. The ability to select samples on
our site is not cookie-driven. We may use session cookies to provide a seamless
experience on the site and to combine with our log files so that we can
understand our site traffic and analyze our demographic information in
aggregate form. If you have set your browser to reject cookies, our site will
not identify you when you enter and you will need to manually type in your ID
and password.
Your Feedback is Always Welcome
We welcome your comments and questions about our privacy policy - or anything
else you might want to talk about. To contact us click:: here
You can reach us via email at “info@africanaquatic.com”
Our Postal Address is:
